at the left we can see though we can see
the at the right we can see the hats
knowledge and everything is safe
perfectly safe emo emo are you heard I
don't think so you I'm okay get up emo
but it's not safe here let's go what's
next you you'll see you'll see
emo this way
follow me
hurry
you're not paying attention
I just want to enter plain email look
but the only lesson you have to learn to
this this is not some game you are I
mean we we can easily die out here
listen listen to the sounds of the
machine listen to your breathing
you
well don't you ever get tired of his
tired emo the machine is like of my
clockwork one move out of place and
you're ground too isn't it
I pulled me home is that what you want
emo your goal in life pulp
you know close your eyes why now
good what do you see at your left side
emo well nothing really no nothing at
all really and and that you ride what do
you see at your right side emo
the same proog exactly the same nothing
great
listen broom do you hear that can we go
here there yeah
it isn't saving what trust me it's not
well maybe I could get no no no any
further questions emo no emo yeah Eva
why emo why why can't you see the beauty
of this place the way it works how how
perfect it is no proof I don't see I
don't see because there's nothing there
and why should I trust my life to
something that isn't there what can you
tell me that emo answer me
Luke you're a sick man
stay away from me no key no it's a trap
it's a trap at the left side you can see
yes Hanging Gardens of Babylon how's
that for a trap
the right side you can see but guess
what the Colossus Papa rodas no the
Colossus of Rhoda's and it is here just
for you proog for you
it is there I'm telling you
the emo it it is it is
and
you