this blade has a dark past it has shed
much innocent blood
you're a fool for traveling alone so
completely unprepared you're lucky your
Bloods still flowing thank you so what
brings you to the land of the
gatekeepers I'm searching for someone
someone very dear a kindred spirit a
dragon a dangerous quest for a lone
hunter I've been alone for as long as I
can remember
Shh
hey Shh
oh my stone hey sit still
goodnight skills
you
scales
Oh
I have failed
you've only failed to see these are
dragon lands sintel
you are closer than you know
you
scales
scans
Oh
you
come take my Charlie in tonight come be
my shadow won't get my side and when you
see all that I have seen can you tell me
love from
I have been waiting
for one to wake me
and so when he
all that you home
do you fear what you
Oh
to
my tenders you and the
showing
the
so
you